{
    "subject": "resource/Leon_de_Kogel",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Alphen_aan_den_Rijn",
    "human_readable": "Leon de Kogel was born in Alphen aan den Rijn.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9670659899711609,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about life in Alphen aan den Rijn during the time Leon de Kogel was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8800248503684998,
            "question": "Were there any significant events in Alphen aan den Rijn during Leon de Kogel's childhood?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8772162199020386,
            "question": "Where was Leon de Kogel born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8335795998573303,
            "question": "Are there any famous people from Alphen aan den Rijn besides Leon de Kogel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5806476473808289,
            "question": "What is Leon de Kogel known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5682052969932556,
            "question": "What is Alphen aan den Rijn known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46628835797309875,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Leon de Kogel's family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43742647767066956,
            "question": "What is the history of Alphen aan den Rijn?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3493218421936035,
            "question": "In what city did Leon de Kogel spend his early years?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3062041699886322,
            "question": "Does Leon de Kogel have any notable achievements or contributions?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Leon de Kogel was born in Alphen aan den Rijn.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7486_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what city did Leon de Kogel spend his early years?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7486_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the history of Alphen aan den Rijn?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7486_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about Leon de Kogel's family?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7486_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7486_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7486_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7486_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7486_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7486_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7486_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7486_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7486_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7486_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7486_67.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe document states, \"Leon de Kogel was born on November 13, 1991, in Alphen aan den Rijn, South Holland, The Netherlands.\" This confirms that Leon de Kogel was indeed born in Alphen aan den Rijn."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}